Guide to the Western Film Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- December 2012 Acquisition, 1911-2006; 4.84; (8 boxes)
  - Cimarron - promotional book, 1931 (Box 51)
  - Cliffhanger - press kit, 1993 (Box 51)
  - Close Encounters of the Third Kind - press kit, 1980 (Box 51)
  - Close Encounters of the Third Kind - promotional book, 1980 (Box 51)
  - Color of Night - press kit, 1994 (Box 51)
  - Colors - press kit, 1987 (Box 51)
  - Continental Divide - press kit, 1981 (Box 51)
  - The Conversation - pressbook, 1974
  - The Covered Wagon - promotional book, 1923 (Box 51)
  - Crocodile Dundee in Los Angeles - press kit, 2001 (Box 51)
  - Dance Me Outside - press kit, 1995 (Box 51)
  - Dangerous Minds - press kit, 1995 (Box 51)
  - Dead Again - press kit, 1991 (Box 51)
  - The Desperate Trail - press kit, 1995
  - Destry Rides Again - pressbook, 1932
  - Don Q, Son of Zorro - promotional book, 1925 (Box 51)
  - Don't Be a Menace to South Central While Drinking Your Juice in the Hood - press kit, 1996 (Box 51)
  - Dream West - press kit, 1986 (Box 51)
  - The Duchess and the Dirtwater Fox - press kit, 1976 (Box 51)
  - Duel in the Sun - promotional book, 1946 (Box 51)
  - Eating Raoul - press kit, 1982 (Box 51)
  - Echo Park - press kit, 1986 (Box 51)
  - The End of Violence - press kit, 1996 (Box 51)
  - The Enforcer - press kit, 1976 (Box 51)
  - Erin Brockovich - press kit, 2000 (Box 51)
  - Erin Brockovich - pressbook, 2000
  - Even Cowgirls Get the Blues - press kit, 1993 (Box 51)
  - The Evening Star - press kit, 1996 (Box 51)
  - Every Which Way But Loose - press kit, 1978 (Box 51)
  - The Falcon and the Snowman - press kit, 1984 (Box 51)
  - Fat Man and Little Boy - press kit, 1989 (Box 51)
  - Friday Night Lights - press kit, 2004; 1 folder, 1 compact disc (Box 51)
    Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services. Disk #: 2012.wa.263.0003. Friday Night Lights
  - Fool for Love - press kit, 1985 (Box 51)
  - Gallopin' Through - pressbook, 1923 (Box 52)
  - Go - press kit, 1999 (Box 52)
  - The Godfather Part II - pressbook, 1974
  - Goin' South - press kit, 1978 (Box 52)
  - Grace of My Heart - press kit, 1996 (Box 52)
  - Grand Isle - press kit, 1989 (Box 52)
  - The Great American Cowboy - press kit, 1973
  - The Great White Hype - press kit, 1996 (Box 52)
  - The Hallelujah Trail - pressbook, 1965 (Box 52)
  - Harry and Tonto - press kit, 1974 (Box 52)
  - Hawaii - promotional book, 1966 (Box 52)
  - Head Over Heels - press kit, 1979 (Box 52)
  - Heat - press kit, 1986 (Box 52)
  - Heaven's Gate - pressbook, 1980
  - Hell Town - press kit, 1985 (Box 52)
  - Heralds and promotional flyers, 1911-1951 (Box 52)
    Includes 29 flyers: 20 Mule Team (1940); Annie Get Your Gun (1951); Arizona (1931); The Barrier (1926); Beau Bandit (1930); The Big Trail (1930); Call of the West (1930); Court-Martial (1928); The Covered Wagon (1923); Debtor to the Law (1919); The Gold Rush (1925); The Golden Princess (1925); The Great Divide (1915); Laughing Boy (1934); The Love Route (1915); Mildred Pierce (1945); My Prairie Flower (1911); Mystery Ranch (1932); One Man Dog (1927); Rainbow Trail (1932); Redskin (1929); Rose-Marie (1928); San Franciso (1936); Sequoia (1934); The Spoilers (1914); Stand Up and Fight (1939); Tiger Shark (1932); Two Men of Sandy Bar (1916); What Price Hollywood (1932).
  - High Anxiety - press kit, 1977 (Box 53)
  - Hollywood Vice Squad - press kit, 1986 (Box 53)
  - Hopalong Cassidy - pressbooks, 1944-1946
    Includes four pressbooks: Forty Thieves (1944), Mystery Man (1944), The Devil's Playground (1946), and Hopalong Cassidy (circa 1945).
  - Houston Knights - press kit, 1987 (Box 53)
  - How Stella Got Her Groove Back - press kit, 1998 (Box 53)
  - How the West Was Won - promotional book, 1962 (Box 53)
  - How to Be a Player - press kit, 1997 (Box 53)
  - I Love You to Death - press kit, 1990 (Box 53)
  - Into the Night - press kit, 1984 (Box 53)
  - Into the West - press kit, 1982 (Box 53)
  - Invasion of the Body Snatchers - press kit, 1978 (Box 53)
  - Invasion of the Body Snatchers - promotional book, 1978 (Box 53)
  - It's A Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World - promotional book, 1963 (Box 53)
  - Jagged Edge - press kit, 1985 (Box 53)
  - Jason's Lyric - press kit, 1994 (Box 53)
  - Keys to Tulsa - press kit, 1996 (Box 53)
  - La Bamba - press kit, 1986 (Box 53)
  - L.A. Story - press kit, 1991 (Box 53)
  - Last Man Standing - press kit, 1996 (Box 53)
  - The Legend of Billie Jean - press kit, 1985 (Box 53)
  - The Legend of the Lone Ranger - press kit, 1981 (Box 53)
  - Lethal Weapon 4 - press kit, 1998 (Box 53)
  - Little Miss Sunshine - press kit, 2006; 1 folder, 1 compact disc (Box 53)
    Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services. Disk #: 2012.wa.263.0004.
  - The Longest Yard - press kit, 2005; 1; (1 CD-ROM) (Box 53)
    Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services. Disk #: 2012.wa.263.0005
  - Mackenna's Gold - promotional book, 1969 (Box 53)
  - Malibu's Most Wanted - press kit, 2003; 1 folder, 1 compact disc (Box 53)
    Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services. Disk #: 2012.wa.263.0002.
  - Marooned - promotional book, 1969 (Box 53)
  - Mask - press kit, 1985 (Box 53)
  - Mike's Murder - press kit, 1983 (Box 53)
  - Modern Romance - press kit, 1981 (Box 54)
  - Mulholland Dr. - promotional book, 2001 (Box 54)
  - My Prairie Flower - flyer, 1911
  - Nevada Smith - press kit, 1991 (Box 54)
  - Never Cry Wolf - press kit, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Nick of Time - press kit, 1995 (Box 54)
  - The Nickel Ride - press kit, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Ocean's Eleven - press kit, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Oklahoma! - promotional book, 1955 (Box 54)
  - Old Gringo - press kit, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Orange County - press kit, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Outland - press kit, 1981 (Box 54)
  - Outlaw Blues - press kit, 1977 (Box 54)
  - The Outsiders - press kit, 1982 (Box 54)
  - Pacific Heights - press kit, 1999 (Box 54)
  - Paint Your Wagon - promotional book, 1969 (Box 54)
  - Pale Rider - pressbook, 1986
  - Panther - press kit, 1995 (Box 54)
  - Pink Cadillac - press kit, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Places in the Heart - pressbook, 1986
  - Posse - press kit, 1975 (Box 54)
  - The Postman Always Rings Twice - pressbook, 1945
  - The Presidio - press kit, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Rafferty and the Gold Dust Twins - press kit, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Rain Man - press kit, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Ray - pressbook, 2004
  - Ride the Wind [Bonanza] - press kit, circa 1966 (Box 54)
  - Rosewood - press kit, 1997 (Box 54)
  - Roy Rodgers - pressbooks, 1942-1951
    Includes ten pressbooks: Down Dakota Way (1949), The Golden Stallion (1949), Grand Canyon Trail (1948), Heart of the Rockies (1951), Song of Arizona (1946), South of Caliente (1951), Sunset in the West (1951), Sunset Serenade (1942), Susanna Pass (1949), and Twilight in the Sierras (1950).
  - San Antonio - pressbook, 1945
  - Serial - press kit, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Set It Off - press kit, 1996 (Box 54)
  - Show Girls - press kit, 1995 (Box 54)
  - The Shining - press kit, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Silent Movie - press kit, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Silkwood - press kit, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Silverado - press kit, 1985 (Box 54)
  - Silver Streak - press kit, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Singles - press kit, 1992 (Box 55)
  - Speed - press kit, 1994 (Box 55)
  - Star 80 - press kit, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Sutter's Gold - pressbook, 1936
  - Suburbia - press kit, 1997 (Box 55)
  - Sunset - press kit, 1988 (Box 55)
  - Swing Shift - press kit, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Talk Radio - press kit, 1988 (Box 55)
  - Tequila Sunrise - press kit, 1988 (Box 55)
  - Terms of Endearment - press kit, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Tex - press kit, 1982 (Box 55)
  - Texasville - press kit, 1990 (Box 55)
  - That's Life - press kit, 1985 (Box 55)
  - The Thin Blue Line - press kit, 1988 (Box 55)
  - They Died with Their Boots On - pressbook, 1941
  - Things Are Tough All Over - press kit, 1982 (Box 55)
  - Thelma & Louise - press kit, 1991 (Box 55)
  - Three the Hard Way - press kit, 1974 (Box 55)
  - To Live and Die in L.A. - press kit, 1985 (Box 55)
  - Tombstone - press kit, 1993 (Box 55)
  - A Touch of Evil (re-edit) - press kit, 1998 (Box 55)
  - The Trip to Bountiful - press kit, 1985 (Box 55)
  - True Confessions - press kit, 1981 (Box 55)
  - True Stories - press kit, 1986 (Box 55)
  - Twilight - press kit, 1998 (Box 55)
  - Unconquered - pressbook, 1947
  - Unforgiven - pressbook, 1992
  - Urban Cowboy - promotional book, 1980 (Box 55)
  - The Vanishing American - promotional book, 1925 (Box 55)
  - Wagons East! - press kit, 1994 (Box 55)
  - Wells Fargo - pressbook, 1937 (Box 55)
  - Westworld - press kit, 1973 (Box 55)
  - What's Love Got to Do with It - press kit, 1993 (Box 55)
  - Wild Bill - press kit, 1995 (Box 55)
  - Oversize material, 1911-2000 (Box 56 (Oversize))
    Includes The Big Sleep, Bugsy, The Conversation, The Desperate Trail, Destry Rides Again, Erin Brokovich, The Godfather: Part II, The Great American Cowboy, Heaven's Gate, Hopalong Cassidy, My Prairie Flower, Pale Rider, Places in the Heart.
  - Oversize material, 1936-2004 (Box 57 (Oversize))
    Includes The Postman Always Rings Twice, Ray, Roy Rodgers, San Antonio, Stutter's Gold, They Died with Their Boots On, Unconquered, Unforgiven, Wells Fargo.
- July 2013 Acquisition, 1916-1981; 0.25; (2 boxes)
  Purchased from Walter Reuben, Inc. on the Arthur Corbitt Hoskins Memorial Fund, 2013.
  Consists of press kits, pressbooks, and souvenir programs.
  - The Blue Dahlia, 1946 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - The Broken Spur, undated (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - The Buccaneer, 1938 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - Cheyenne Autumn, 1964 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - Citizen Kane, 1940 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - Cupid's Brand, undated (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - Cyclone Bliss, undated (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - Dead or Alive, undated (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - Devil-Dog Dawson, undated (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - East of Eden, 1981 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - Fistful of Dollars, 1964 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - The Flaming Frontier, 1926 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - Fort Apache, 1948 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - The Godfather, Part II, 1974 (Box 58 (Oversize))
  - The Gold Rush, 1925 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - Gun Crazy, 1950 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - Hills of Hate, undated (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - The Lady of Shanghai, 1948 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - The Man from Nowhere, undated (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, 1975 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - Ramona, 1916 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - Red River, 1948 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - The Searchers, 1956 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - The Sheriff of Hope Eternal, undated (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - A Streetcar Named Desire, 1951 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - They Drive by NIght, 1940 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - T-Men, 1947 (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - The Trail of 98, undated (Box 59 (Oversize))
  - Treasure of Sierra Madre, 1948 (Box 59 (Oversize))
- 14 October 2013 Acquisition, 1921-1928; 0.00; 1 broadside
  - $5,000 Reward, 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Arizona Wildcat, 1927 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Black Jack, 1927 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Blood Will Tell, 1927 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - The Branded Sombrero, 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Cameo Kirby, circa 1927 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Chain Lightning, 1927 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - The Cowboy Kid, 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - A Daredevil's Reward, circa 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Hello, Cheyenne!, 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Horseman of the Plains, 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - The Iron Horse, 1924 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Painted Post, circa 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Pajamas, circa 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Shame, 1921 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Silver Valley, circa 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Singed, 1927 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Tumbling River, circa 1927 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Wild West Romance, 1928 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Wolf Fangs, circa 1927 (Box 61 (Broadside))
- Restricted Fragile Material, 0.21; (1 box)
  Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Computer disks (2012.wa.13.001; 2012.wa.263.0002-2012.wa.263.0005) (Box 60)